BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 18) 6178/018
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Code 2589: USWA/Silver Bell Mining, LLC, 2001-2004 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Code 2590: UAW Local No. 1050/United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America/Aluminum Company of America, 1974-2001 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Code 2592: USWA/Aluminum Company of America, 1986-2002 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Code 2610: USWA, 1980-2001 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Code 2674: USWA/Noranda Aluminum, Inc., 1989-2002 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  Local 7686
- Code 2920: International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers District 66/Trane Company, 1995-2004 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  La Crosse Trane Lodge 21
- Code 2957: U.A.A.A.I.W.A. Local 833/Kohler Co., 1990-2002 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Code 3203: Paper, Allied-Industrial, Chemical, and Energy Workers International Union/Briggs and Stratton Corporation, 1986- 2006 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  Local 7232
- Code 3208: Diesel Workers Union/Cummins Engine Company Inc., 1984-1993 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Code 3209: Office Committee Union/Cummins Engine Company Inc., 1993-1999 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Code 3217: UAW Local 163/Detroit Diesel Corporation, 1994-1998 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  8/26/1994-8/30/1998
- Code 3222: U.A.A.A.I.W.A./Deere and Company, 1995-2009 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Code 3226: UAW/Navistar International Transportation Corp., 1995-2002 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  10/16/1995-10/1/2002
- Code 3227: International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers, and Helpers/Whirlpool Corporation, 1997- 2002 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  8/1/1997-8/3/2002
- Code 3233: International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers/Caterpillar, 1994-2005 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  Local Lodge No. 851; 12/5/1994-5/1/2005
- Code 3278: USWA/Timken Company, 1989-2004 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Code 3291: International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers/Maytag Corporation, 1992-1999 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Code 3294: International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried, Machine and Furniture Workers/Copeland Corporation, 1979- 2001 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Code 3298: International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Technical, Salaried, Machine and Furniture Workers/Connersville Plant, 1988- 2005 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  Local 919
- Code 3299: USWA Local 2395/Tecumseh Products Company, 1980-2006 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  9/4/1980-10/31/2006
- Code 3311: Sheet Metal Workers International Association/Carrier Corporation, 1979-2000 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  Local Union 527; 11/5/1979-11/5/2000
- Code 3314: International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers/Tecumseh Products Co., 1983-1998 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  Lodge 1259; 6/30/1983-6/30/1998
- Code 3319: U.A.A.A.I.W.A./Case Corporation, 1990-1998 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  Local Union 1304 and 180; 6/2/1990- 3/29/1998
- Code 3320: I.A.M.A.W. Local 2003/DynCorp, 1992-2002 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  5/4/1992-5/5/2002; 1 of 2
- Code 3320: I.A.M.A.W. Local 2003/DynCorp, 1989-2005 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  5/1/1989-5/1/2005; 2 of 2
- Code 3348: UAW/Caterpillar Inc., 1983-2004 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  4/19/1983-12/15/2004; 1 of 2
- Code 3348: UAW/Caterpillar Inc., 1998-2004 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  3/16/1998-4/1/2004; 2 of 2
- Code 3366: USWA/Rheem Manufacturing Company, 1994-2003 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  Local 9326; 12/16/1994- 12/15/2003
- Code 3367: International Association of Machinists Lodge 1947/Mercury Marine, 1994-2000 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  6/13/1994-6/18/2000
- Code 3374: Lufkin Industries, Inc./A.F.L.-C.I.O., 1996-2002 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  10/7/1996-10/7/2002
- Code 3375: USWA Local 1999/Carrier Corporation, 1999-2002 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Code 3389: I.A.M.A.W./The Trane Company, 1990-2006 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Code 3393: Sheet Metal Workers International Association Local 483/Carrier Corporation, 1994-2004 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  5/1/1994-2/3/2004
- Code 3394: USWA/Hussmann Corporation, 1996-2000 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  12/21/1996-12/22/2000
- Code 3395: USWA Local 7893/ Rheem Manufacturing Company, 1986-2003 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Code 3400: International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried, Machine and Furniture Workers/The Trane Company, 1990- 2002 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  Local 782
- Code 3401: Bricklayers and Allied Craftsmen/Eastern Contractors Association, Inc., 1991-1997 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  6/1/1991-5/31/1997
- Code 3600: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers No. 2249/GE Appliances--Bloomington, Inc., 1997-2003 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Code 3617: International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried, Machine and Furniture Workers/General Electric Company, 1988- 2003 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Code 3618: United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America/General Electric Company, 1988-2003 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Code 3634: U.A.A.A.I.W.A. No. 442/Webster City Plant, 1996-2005 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Code 3635: U.A.A.A.I.W.A. Local 137, 1986-2005 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Code 3637: UAW Local 997/Maytag Company, 1989-2004 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Code 3645: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 3/Lighting Manufacturers Group, 1989-2001 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Code 3651: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers No. 1362/Rockwell International Corporation, 1989-2003 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Code 3658: International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried, Machine and Furniture Workers Local 796/Philips Consumer Electronics Company, 1995-2003 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Code 3660: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers/Thomson Consumer Electronics Inc., 1995-2001 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Code 3683: AT&T/International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  28 May 1995; 1 of 4
- Code 3683: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers/Lucent Technologies/Celestica Inc., 1998-2003 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  Local Union 2021; 5/31/1998-5/31/2003; 2 of 4
- Code 3683: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers/Lucent Technologies/Celestica Inc., 1998-2003 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  Local Union 2021; 5/31/1998-5/31/2003; 3 of 4
- Code 3683: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers/Lucent Technologies/Celestica Inc., 1998-2003 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  Local Union 2021; 5/31/1998-5/31/2003; 4 of 4
- Code 3689: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers/AT&T, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  Local Union 2020; 6/1/1986; 1 of 3
- Code 3689: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers/AT&T, 1995-1998 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  Local Union 2020; 5/28/1995-5/30/1998; 2 of 3
- Code 3689: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers/Lucent Technologies, 1998-2003 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  Local Union 2020; 5/31/1998-5/31/2003; 3 of 3
- Code 3695: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers/Raytheon Company, 1991-1998 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  Local Union 1505; 1 of 3
- Code 3695: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers/Raytheon Company, 1989-2004 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  Local Union 1505; 1989-1991 and 2000-2004; 2 of 3
- Code 3695: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers/Raytheon Company, 1998-2000 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  Local Union 1505; 8/30/1998-8/26/2000; 3 of 3
- Code 3739: Allied Industrial Workers/United Paperworkers/Whirlpool Corporation, 1986-2002 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  Local 7370; 9/9/1986-9/9/1989 and 11/23/1992-10/1/1997 and 10/2/1997-9/29/2002
- Code 3772: International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers No. 1526/Amana Company, 1989-2007 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Code 3778: International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried, Machine and Furniture Workers No. 808/Whirlpool Corporation, 1992- 2004 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  2/17/1992-2/17/1996 and 2/19/1996-2/19/2000 and 2/19/2000-2/19/2004
- Code 3782: IUE/Delphi Automotive Systems, 1999-2003 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  11/22/1999-11/15/2003; 1 of 2
- Code 3782: IUE-CWA/Delphi Corporation, 2003-2007 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  12/1/2003-10/12/2007; 2 of 2
- Code 3784: Sidney Lodge No. 1529 of the I.A.M.A.W./Amphenol Corporation, 1986-2004 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Code 3786: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers/Hoover Company, 1986-1992 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  Local No. 1985; 1 of 2
- Code 3786: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers/Hoover Company, 1995-2005 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  Local No. 1985; 2 of 2
- Code 4004: UAW No. 2383/Budd Company, 1998-2001 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  11/16/1998-11/9/2001 and 11/10/2001- 2/6/2005
- Code 4005: UAW No. 287/Borg-Warner Automotive, 1986-1998 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Code 4005: UAW No. 287/Borg-Warner Automotive, 1998-2001 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  3/12/1998-3/12/2001; 2 of 2
- Code 4006: UAW/Budd Company, 1991-2000 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  11/4/1991-10/31/1995 and 11/1/1995-10/31/2000
- Code 4006: UAW/Budd Company, 2001-2005 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  Locals 306, 813, and 757; 2/26/2001-10/28/2005
- Code 4007/Code 4010: UAW/DaimlerChrysler Corporation, 1999-2003 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  9/27/1999-9/14/2003
- Code 4007/Code 4010: UAW/Chrysler Corporation, 1996-1999 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  10/14/1996-9/14/1999
- Code 4007: UAW/DaimlerChrysler Corporation, 2003-2007 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  9/29/2003-9/14/2007
- Code 4010: UAW/Chrysler Corporation, 1988-1999 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  5/16/1988-9/14/1990, 11/19/1990-9/14/1993, 10/14/1996-9/14/1999; 1 of 2
- Code 4010: UAW/DaimlerChrysler Corporation, 1999-2003 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  9/27/1999-9/14/2003; 2 of 2
- Code 4014: Paper, Allied-Industrial, Chemical and Energy Workers International Union/United Paperworkers/Dana Corporation, 1996- 2002 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  Local Union 6-903/7903; 1/28/1996-1/29/1999 and 1/30/1999-1/28/2002
- Code 4015: UAW/Dana Corporation, 1995-2001 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  12/4/1995-12/7/1998 and 11/23/1998-12/3/2001
- Code 4019: UAW/Ford Motor Company, 1999-2003 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  10/9/1999-9/14/2003; 1 of 2
- Code 4019: UAW/Ford Motor Company, 2003-2007 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  9/15/2003-9/14/2007; 2 of 2
- Code 4020: UAW Local 1621/Murray Inc., 1993-2002 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  11/1/1993-9/1/1996, 9/1/1996-9/4/1999, 9/4/1999-8/31/2002
- Code 4022: UAW/General Motors Corporation, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  9/28/1999
- Code 4022: UAW/General Motors Corporation, 2003-2007 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  9/18/2003-9/14/2007; 1 of 2
- Code 4022: UAW/General Motors Corporation, 2003-2007 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  9/18/2003-9/14/2007; 2 of 2
- Code 4023: UAW/Saturn, 1995-2003 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Code 4036: UAW/Meritor Automotive Inc., 1997-2000 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  7/19/1997-7/19/2000
- Code 4040: Smith Steel Workers No. 19806/A.O. Smith Automotive Products Company, 1995-1999 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  8/1995-7/31/1999
- Code 4046: UAW No. 12/Chrysler Corporation, 1987-2003 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Code 4049: International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers/Raytheon Aircraft Company, 1990-2001 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  8/6/1990-8/1/1993 and 8/5/1996-8/5/2001
- Code 4050: UAW No. 218/Bell Helicopter Textron Inc., 1996-2006 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  6/10/1996-6/11/2000, 6/11/2000- 6/15/2003, 6/16/2003-6/11/2006
- Code 4051: UAW/AlliedSignal Inc., 1999-2003 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  5/3/1999-5/3/2003
- Code 4052: International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers/Learjet, 1990-2000 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  District No. 70, Local No. 639; 11/5/1990-11/1993 and 11/4/1996-10/2/2000
- Code 4055: SPEEA/Boeing Company, 1992-2002 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  12/2/1992-12/1/1995, 12/2/1995-12/1/1999, 3/20/2000-12/1/2002; 1 of 2
- Code 4055: SPEEA/Boeing Company, 2002-2005 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Code 4056: International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers/Boeing Company, 1992-1995 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  10/4/92-10/3/95; 1 of 2
- Code 4056: International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers/Boeing Company, 1995-2002 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  12/14/1995-9/1/1999 and 9/2/1999-9/1/2002; 2 of 2
- Code 4057: UAW No. 1069/Boeing Helicopters, 1992-2002 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  10/18/1992-10/4/1995, 1/22/1996- 9/1/1999, 9/2/1999-9/1/2002
- Code 4058: IAM/Cessna Aircraft Company, 1993-2001 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  7/26/93-10/13/96 and 10/13/96- 10/13/2001
- Code 4065: International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers No. 725/McDonnell Douglas Corporation, 1996-2002 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  2/5/1996-10/24/1999 and 10/29/1999-10/27/2002
- Code 4066: UAW No. 148/Douglas Aircraft Company, 1991-2000 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  3/18/1991-4/16/1995 and 4/17/1995-4/30/2000
- Code 4073: IAM/Aeronautical Industrial District Lodge 776/Lockheed Martin Aeronautics Company, 1993-2006 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  12/20/93-4/6/97, 4/7/97-4/9/2000, 4/27/2000-4/13/2003, 4/28/03-4/9/06; 1 of 2
- Code 4073: IAM/Aeronautical Industrial District Lodge 776/Lockheed Martin Aeronautics Company, 2003-2006 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  4/28/2003-4/9/2006; 2 of 2
- Code 4080: IAM/Aeronautical Industrial District Lodge 725/Lockheed Martin Skunk Works, 1996-2002 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  3/2/1996-3/1/1999 and 3/2/1999-3/1/2002
- Code 4081: IAM/Aeronautical Machinists Lodge 709/Lockheed Martin Aeronautical Systems, 1990-2002 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  3/5/1990-3/1/1993, 4/22/1996-3/1/1999, 3/10/1999-3/1/2002
- Code 4083: IAM No. 837/McDonnell Douglas Corporation, 1996-2001 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  5/20/1996-5/20/2001
- Code 4084: UAW/Rockwell International Corporation, 1990-1999 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  7/7/1990-6/27/1993, 6/26/1993- 6/24/1996, 6/25/1996-6/21/1999
- Code 4088: IAM/Rohr Inc., 1993-2003 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  2/15/1993-2/15/1996, 2/12/1996-2/13/2000, 6/21/1999- 2/16/2003; Aeronautical Mechanics Lodge 755 and Aerospace/Defense Industry Lodge 725
- Code 4093: Teamsters Union No. 1150/Sikorsky Aircraft Company, 1990-2006 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  2/15/90-2/14/93, 2/15/93-2/18/96, 2/19/96-2/14/99, 2/15/99-2/17/02, 2/18/02-2/19/06
- Code 4095: IAM No. 743/Hamilton Sundstrand Corporation, 2001-2007 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  5/7/2001-5/2/2004 and 5/3/2004-5/6/2007
- Code 4096: IAM No. 91/Pratt and Whitney, 2001-2004 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  12/3/01-12/2/04; 1 of 2
- Code 4096: IAM No. 91/Pratt and Whitney, 1991-2004 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  12/9/91-12/4/96, 12/4/95-12/6/98, 10/8/98- 12/2/01, 12/3/01-12/2/04
- Code 4099: IAM No. S6/Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers No. 4/Bath Iron Works Corporation, 1997-2000 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  8/25/1997-8/27/2000
- Code 4103: Metal Trades Council/General Dynamics Corporation, 1984-1995 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  12/30/84-6/30/88 (Book 1 and 2) and 6/30/91-7/2/95; 1 of 2
- Code 4103: Metal Trades Council/General Dynamics Corporation, 1995-2008 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  7/3/95-6/26/98, 6/27/98-6/29/2001, 11/1/99-10/29/2004, 8/1/03-11/7/08; 2 of 2
- Code 4104: UAW No. 571/General Dynamics Company, 1990-2002 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  8/26/90-8/28/93, 7/29/96- 7/31/99, 8/1/99-7/26/2002
- Code 4105: Pascagoula Metal Trades Council/Ingalls Shipbuilding Inc., 1993-2003 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  2/7/93-2/11/96, 2/11/96-5/16/99, 6/7/99-3/2/2003
- Code 4107: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers No. 733/Ingalls Shipbuilding Inc., 1990-2003 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  2/4/90-2/7/93, 2/7/93-2/11/96, 2/11/96-5/16/99, 6/7/99-3/2/2003
- Code 4108: United Steelworkers/Newport News Shipbuilding, 1991-2004 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  4/1/91-2/5/95, 2/6/95-4/4/99, 7/26/99-6/6/2004
- Code 4109: New Orleans Metal Trades Council/Northrop Grumman Ship Systems, 2003-2007 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  6/30/2003-3/4/2007
- Code 4129: International Association of Bridge, Structural, and Ornamental Ironworkers No. 627/National Steel and Shipbuilding Company, 1970-1998 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  10/1/70-9/30/75, 10/1/75-9/30/78, 10/1/78-9/30/81, 10/1/81-9/30/84, 10/1/84-9/30/87
- Code 4133: UAW/Mack Trucks Inc., 1992-2001 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  10/28/1992-10/30/1998 and 7/20/1998-10/1/2001
- Code 4134: International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers No. 684/Norfolk Shipbuilding and Drydock Corporation, 1991-2007 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  3/11/91-10/31/94, 11/1/95-10/31/97, 2/9/98-2/8/2001, 2/9/2001-2/8/2004, 2/9/2004-2/8/2007
- Code 4154: UAW No. 5/AM General Corporation, 1991-1998 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  8/12/1991-8/7/1994 and 8/8/1994- 9/26/1998
- Code 4164: UAW No. 2488/Mitsubishi, 1995-2001 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  8/27/1995-8/27/1998 and 8/27/1998- 8/23/2001
- Code 4177: SPEEA/Boeing Company, 1992-1999 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  12/2/1992-12/1/1995 and 12/2/1995-12/1/1999; 1 of 2
- Code 4177: SPEEA/Boeing Company, 2000-2005 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  3/20/2000-12/1/2002 and 12/2/2002-12/1/2005; 2 of 2
- Code 4183: UAW No. 1243/Howmet Corporation, 1981-1997 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  6/1/1981-6/1/1985, 6/1/1985-6/1/1988, 6/1/1994-6/1/1997; 1 of 2
- Code 4183: UAW No. 1243/Howmet Corporation, 1997-2005 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  6/1/1997-6/1/2002 and 1/1/1999- 6/1/2005; 2 of 2
- Code 4193: APSA/Aerospace Corporation, 2001-2004 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  8/1/2001-8/1/2002, 8/1/2002-8/1/2003, 8/1/2003-8/1/2004
- Code 4194: UAW No. 533/AlliedSignal Automotive, 1993-2001 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  10/29/1993-10/28/1998 and 7/20/1998-10/31/2001
- Code 4195: IAM No. 175/Harley-Davidson Motor Company, 1987-2007 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  2/2/87-2/2/91, 2/2/91-2/2/94, 2/2/97-2/2/02 and 2/2/01-2/2/07
- Code 4197: UAW/New United Motor Manufacturing Inc., 1985-2001 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  7/1/85-6/30/88, 7/1/88-6/30/91, 7/1/91-7/31/94, 8/1/94-7/31/98, 8/1/98-8/4/01
- Code 4201: Metal Trades/Todd Pacific Shipyards Corporation, 1990-2002 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  4/1/1990-3/31/1993, 4/1/1993-7/31/1996, 11/24/1997-7/31/1999 and 8/1/1999-7/31/2002
- Code 4203: IAM/Freightliner Corporation, 1988-2004 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  District No. 24, Local No. 1005. 1988-1991, 7/1/1991-7/1/1994, 7/1/1997-7/1/2000 and 7/1/2001-7/1/2004.
- Code 4205: UAW No. 5285/Freightliner Corporation, 1994-2006 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  12/18/1994-12/19/1997, 12/22/1997- 12/15/2000, 12/18/2000-12/19/2003 and 6/19/2003-6/19/2006
- Code 4206: URW No. 87/General Motors Corporation, 1995-2000 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  1/11/1995-1/31/2000
- Code 4208: IAM/Boeing Company, 1997-2003 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  District No. 776, Local No. 2317. 12/13/1997- 12/15/2001, 4/17/2003 and 6/6/2003.
- Code 4209: SPEEA/Boeing Company, 1999-2008 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  12/6/1999-12/5/2002 and 7/7/2004-2/19/2008
- Code 4211: UAW/ Delphi Automotive Systems, 1999-2003 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  9/28/1999-9/14/2003; 1 of 3
- Code 4211: UAW/Delphi Automotive Systems, 1999-2003 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  9/28/1999-9/14/2003; 2 of 3
- Code 4211: UAW/Delphi Automotive Systems, 1999-2003 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  9/28/1999-9/14/2003; 3 of 3
- Code 4215: UAW No. 3520/Freightliner, 2003-2007 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  12/20/2003-3/31/2007
- Code 4409: Teamsters No. 1145/Honeywell Inc., 1991-2002 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  1/31/91-1/31/94, 1/31/94-1/31/98 and 1/31/98-1/31/2002
- Code 4412: International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried, Machine and Furniture Workers/Lockheed Martin/Martin Marietta Corporation, 1994-2002 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  6/27/94-6/28/98 and 6/29/98-6/30/2002
- Code 4427: Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union-Xerographic Division/Xerox Corporation, 1992-2001 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  3/22/1992-3/20/1995 and 4/27/1994-3/18/2001
- Code 4611: URW/USW/IAM/Armstrong World Industries, 1986-2002 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  11/2/86-10/31/89, 11/5/89- 10/31/92, 11/1/92-10/31/95, 11/15/92-11/15/95, 5/5/96-3/31/99 and 4/16/99-4/16/02
- Code 4617: Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union No. 224 of the UFCW/Milton Bradley Company, 1997-2003 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  1/31/97-1/30/00 and 1/31/00-1/30/03
- Code 5032: Hawaii Teamsters and Allied Workers No. 996/Oahu Transit Services, 1989-2003 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  7/1/89- 6/30/93, 7/1/93-6/30/96, 7/1/00-6/30/03
- Code 5033: Amalgamated Transit Union/Greyhound Lines, 1993-2004 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  5/26/1993-1/31/1999 and 10/1/1998-1/31/2004
- Code 5201: International Brotherhood of Teamsters/National Master Freight, 1994-2003 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  4/1/1994- 3/31/1998 and 4/1/1998-3/31/2003
- Code 5202: International Brotherhood of Teamsters/National Master Freight, 1994-2003 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  4/1/1994- 3/31/1998 and 4/1/1998-3/31/2003 (2 Books)
- Code 5209: International Brotherhood of Teamsters/National Master Automobile Transporters, 1988-2003 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  6/1/1988-5/31/1991, 5/22/1995-5/31/1999, and 6/1/1999-5/31/2003
- Code 5217: International Brotherhood of Teamsters/Movers and Warehousemen's Association, 1986-2005 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  4/1/86-3/31/89, 4/1/89-3/31/92, 4/1/92-3/31/94, 4/1/94-3/31/96, 4/1/96-3/31/99, 4/1/99-5/10/02, and 6/22/02-4/30/05
- Code 5255: International Brotherhood of Teamsters/National Master United Parcel Service, 1990-2002 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  8/1/1990-7/31/1993, 8/1/1993-7/31/1997, 8/1/1997-7/31/2002
- Code 5271: Teamsters No. 705/United Parcel Service, 1973-2002 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  7/1/1973-4/30/1976, 5/1/1976- 4/30/1979, 5/1/1979-4/30/1982, 5/1/1982-6/1/1985, 8/1/1993-7/31/1997, 8/1/1997-7/31/2002
- Code 5273: Teamsters No. 705/TMI/Illinois Trucking Labor Relations Association, 1994-2003 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  4/1/1994-3/31/1998 and 4/1/1998-3/31/2003
- Code 5274: Teamsters No. 705/Motor Carrier Labor Advisory Council, 1994-2003 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Code 5302: Communications Workers of America District 4/Verizon North, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Code 5401: ILA/United States Maritime Alliance/Carriers Container Council, 1996-2004 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  10/1/96- 9/30/01 and 10/1/01-9/30/04
- Code 5419: Seafarers International Union/Standard Freight, 1996-2006 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  6/16/1996-6/15/2001 and 6/16/2001-6/15/2006
- Code 5420: Seafarers International Union/Standard Tanker, 1996-2006 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Code 5422: International Longshore and Warehouse Union/Pacific Maritime Association, 1996-2002 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  7/1/96-7/1/99 and 7/1/99-7/1/02
- Code 5424: International Longshore and Warehouse Union/Pacific Maritime Association, 1996-1999 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  7/1/96-7/1/99; 1 of 2
- Code 5424: International Longshore and Warehouse Union/Pacific Maritime Association, 1999-2002 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  7/1/1999-7/1/2002; 2 of 2
- Code 5433: ILA/Great Lakes Stevedore Employers Group, 1990-2001 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  1/1/90-12/31/93, 1/1/91- 12/31/94, and 1/1/97-12/31/01
- Code 5700: CWA/AT&T, 1998-2002 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  5/10/1998-5/11/2002; 1 of 2
- Code 5700: CWA/AT&T, 1998-2002 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  5/10/1998-5/11/2002; 2 of 2
- Code 5701: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers/AT&T, 1998-2002 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  5/10/1998-5/11/2002
- Code 5702: Pennsylvania Telephone Guild (CWA)/Bell Atlantic/Verizon Pennsylvania Inc., 1995-2008 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  Local 13500. 8/9/92-8/5/95, 8/6/95-8/8/98, 8/11/98-8/5/00, 8/6/00-8/2/03 and 8/3/03-8/2/08
- Code 5703: CWA/Verizon Pennsylvania Inc., 2000-2008 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  Local 13000. 8/6/00-8/2/03 and 8/3/03- 8/2/08
- Code 5705: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers/Bell Atlantic/Verizon Pennsylvania Inc., 1986-2003 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  Local 1944. 8/10/1986-8/1989, 8/9/1992-8/5/95, 5/21/1995-8/5/2000, 10/9/1998-8/10/2000 and 10/27/2000-8/2/2003
- Code 5707: CWA/Verizon, 2000-2008 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  8/6/2000-8/2/2003 and 8/3/2003-8/2/2008
- Code 5712: CWA/Cincinnati Bell Telephone Company, 1990-2002 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  5/13/90-5/8/93, 5/9/93-5/11/96, 5/12/96-5/8/99 and 5/9/99-5/11/02
- Code 5713: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers/ GTE/Verizon North Incorporated, 1997-2003 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  Local 1106. 9/21/97-9/30/00 and 10/1/00-9/27/03
- Code 5715: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers/GTE North-Pennsylvania, 1995-2001 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  Locals 1451,1635, 1636 and 1637. 11/5/1995-10/31/1998 and 11/1/1998-10/27/2001. 1 of 2.
- Code 5715: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers/GTE North-Pennsylvania, 1992-1995 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  Locals 1451, 1635, 1636 and 1637. 11/20/1992-11/4/1995. 2 of 2.
- Code 5716: International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers No. 824/GTE Florida Inc., 1996-2002 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  7/28/1996-7/31/1999 and 8/1/1999-8/3/2002. 1 of 2.